Tanner Eschmann

Full Stack Engineer Vero Beach. FL 32967

772-766-2918 | eschmanntanner@gmail.com | LinkedIn | Portfolio | Github

SKILLS

Programming Languages: HTML | CSS | Python | JavaScript

Frameworks: NodeJS | Django | Express | Flask | React | Bootstrap | jQuery | JWT | Bcrypt

Databases: postgreSQL | Sequelize | MongoDB | Mongoose Tools: Mocha | Chai | Express Authentication | Postman

Spoken Languages: English, Fluent | Spanish, intermediate | French, Beginner

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING PROJECTS

Software Engineering Immersive | General Assembly | Remote

May 2022 - Dec 2022

Successfully completed 500+ hours of expert-led instruction in Fullstack Engineering fundamentals and the industry's most in-demand technologies, including but not limited to the MERN stack, Python, Django, HTML, CSS, Postman, and PostgreSQL. Developed projects include:

- Hoppy Havoc: Single player game mimicking Flappy Bird using HTML 5, CSS, and Javascript.
- **GitFit**: Fitness App utilizing HTML, CSS, Javascript, PostgreSQL, NodeJS, Express Authentication, and Heroku to form an app geared towards people concerned with their health.
- **Generous**: Philanthropy App which utilizes HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, MongoDB, NodeJS, Express, Express Authentication, and Heroku in order to build out an app geared towards anyone with an altruistic side. Connected to various nonprofit-organizations via an API. Allows users to see & donate to nonprofits associated with a given search.
- **Spiel**: Full-Stack social media app designed using the MERN stack.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Indian River Estates, ACTS Retirement Life Communities, INC.

April 2019 - August 2022

- Server, Host, Dishwasher, Line/Bistro Cook Vero Beach, FL
 - Host: Coordinated a dining room of teenage servers in order to ensure customer satisfaction and efficiency.
 - **Dishwasher:** Worked 60 hour + weeks on a regular basis in order to mitigate workplace chaos amidst a COVID-related worker shortage.
 - Bistro Cook: Designed menus & recipes and led bistro operations during my supervisor's days off.

Marsh Landing Restaurant

October 2017 - October 2018

Runner, Busser, Dishwasher - Fellsmere, FL

EDUCATION

Indian River State College, Vero Beach, FL Bachelor of Science, Aerospace Engineering

Anticipated Graduation: Month/Year

CERTIFICATES

General Assembly - Remote

May 2022 - Dec 2022, Software Engineering